const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אֹהֶל',
    answers: ['tent'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֱמֶת',
    answers: ['trouw', 'waarheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֵשׁ',
    answers: ['vuur', 'bliksem'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'דָּם',
    answers: ['bloed'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'זָהָב',
    answers: ['goud'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חַיָּה',
    answers: ['levend dier', 'dier', 'levend wezen', 'wezen', 'menigte'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חָכְמָה',
    answers: ['wijsheid', 'bedrevenheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חֶסֶד',
    answers: ['goedheid', 'liefde', 'trouw', 'goedertierenheid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יַיִן',
    answers: ['wijn'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'כּוֹכָב',
    answers: ['ster'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'כֶּסֶף',
    answers: ['zilver', 'geld'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מַלְכָּה',
    answers: ['koningin'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מִצְרַיִם',
    answers: ['Egypte'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'סוּס',
    answers: ['paard'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עֵת',
    answers: ['tijd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רֵעַ',
    answers: ['naaste', 'medemens', 'buur', 'vriend'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'פֶּה',
    answers: ['mond'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'תְּהוֹם',
    answers: ['diep water', 'oerzee', 'wateren'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson9Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson9-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 9 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson9Vocabulary
